(Bernadette:)Count your blessings
(Bernadette:)you're not a Tanzanian chimp.
(Policeman:)What?
(Penny:)Don't listen to her--
(Penny:)she's had a lot
of ice cream.
(Penny:)Do you want to join us?
(Priya:)Oh, thank you,
but I have work to do.
(Amy:)Four women walk
down the stairs--
(Amy:)how many reach the lobby?
(Leonard:)Did your sister say anything
when you got home last night?
(Raj:)Oh, no, don't put me
in the middle of this.
(Raj:)I'm not going to
be your go-between.
(Leonard:)Come on, help me out.
(Leonard:)Am I in trouble?
(sighs) There's no
reason to worry.
(Leonard:)That's a relief.
(Raj:)I'm sure
many women
(Raj:)in happy relationships
spend their nights
(Raj:)Skyping with their
ex-boyfriend Sanjay.
(Howard:)Good news, gentlemen--
I found our hacker.
(Todd:)- What?
- Really?
(Howard:)Yeah. No one can hide from me,
(Howard:)not Waldo, not Carmen San Diego,
(Howard:)not even topless
Natalie Portman.
(Sheldon:)I've never said
these words before,